<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Heliacal Club</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Heliacal Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:55:41 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Law of One</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/lawofone1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:55:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/lawofone1/</guid>
      <description>Read the channelings at https://lawofone.info/ to develop yor own interpretation of this school of thought.The Law of One is a spiritual and philosophical concept that is based on the belief that all things in the universe are ultimately interconnected and are part of a single, unified consciousness.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Kundalini Tantra: Part 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/kundalini2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:51:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/kundalini2/</guid>
      <description>Kundalini is a spiritual and energetic concept in Hinduism and yoga that refers to the awakening of a dormant energy located at the base of the spine. The concept of Kundalini has been embraced by many people as a means of achieving spiritual enlightenment and self-realization.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Kundalini Tantra</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/kundalini/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/kundalini/</guid>
      <description>Kundalini awakening refers to the activation and ascent of Kundalini energy, a type of spiritual energy believed to reside within the human body. According to some spiritual traditions, Kundalini energy is said to be coiled like a serpent at the base of the spine, and its awakening is thought to be associated with a range of spiritual and physical experiences.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 09:10:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Heliacal Social&gt;Heliacal Social # The future will be based on the blockchain according to what we can predict with the present information about the internet. Learning this information inspired me to develop multiple decentralized web apps ready to be launched when the next crypto wave hits the media and internet.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Gnosticism</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/gnostic1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 08:36:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/gnostic1/</guid>
      <description>Gnosticism is a term that refers to a diverse set of religious movements that flourished in the early centuries of the Common Era, particularly in the Mediterranean world.
At its core, Gnosticism is characterized by the belief that knowledge (gnosis in Greek) is the key to achieving salvation.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hermetic Laws of the Universe</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hermetics2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:54:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hermetics2/</guid>
      <description>The Hermetic laws of the universe are a set of principles that describe how the universe functions and how we can align ourselves with these principles in order to manifest our desires and create positive change in our lives.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Hermeticism</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hermetics1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:42:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hermetics1/</guid>
      <description>Hermeticism is a philosophical and spiritual movement that emerged in ancient Greece and Egypt, and is named after the mythical figure Hermes Trismegistus. It is a multifaceted tradition that combines elements of Greek philosophy, Egyptian mythology, and Jewish and Christian teachings.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astrology</title>
      <link>http://example.org/astrology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/astrology/</guid>
      <description>Astrology Service&gt;Astrology Service # Discover your unique astrological blueprint and unlock your true potential with our comprehensive reading service! Our expert astrologers will delve into the mysteries of your Nordic, I-Ching, and Western astrological charts to reveal your life purpose and guide you on your journey to self-discovery and fulfillment.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>