<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heliacal Club</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Heliacal Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Christ Consciousness &amp; Light Bodies (Merkaba)</title><link>/posts/gnosis-merkaba/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/gnosis-merkaba/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Christ Consciousness?> What&amp;rsquo;s Christ Consciousness? # Christ Consciousness is a state of consciousness in which you have formed a union with your divine self which is also a part of your creative mind.
Your abilities from this life and maybe some from other lifetimes feel as natural as breathing air during christ consciousness.
To achieve this state, you must learn how to flow with the divinity within your mind. You must be able to recognize your conscious mind from your subconscious mind.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/gnosis-merkaba/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Nature harmonizes us</title><link>/posts/natureharmony/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/natureharmony/</guid><description>The harmonous effects Nature energy produces in the body &amp;amp; mind</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/natureharmony/cover.png"/></item><item><title>The Hermetic Laws of the Universe</title><link>/posts/hermeticlaws/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/hermeticlaws/</guid><description>Hermetic laws of the Universe</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/hermeticlaws/cover.png"/></item><item><title>The Planetary Energy Grid</title><link>/posts/gnosis-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/gnosis-1/</guid><description>Introspections> Introspections # There exists a blue etheric energy grid surrounding our planet. I theorize it&amp;rsquo;s responsible for keeping Souls trapped in the planetary matrix (system). This is also a common belief for those who have discovered the grid actually zapping our mental atom upon death resulting in what you have faith in being presented to you. TODO: This topic needs more research and a lot more discussion.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/gnosis-1/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Transmigration of the Human Soul</title><link>/posts/gnosis-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/gnosis-3/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Soul Transmigration?> What&amp;rsquo;s Soul Transmigration? # The transmigration of the human soul, also known as reincarnation or rebirth, is a concept that has been embraced by spiritual traditions around the world for thousands of years. The origins of this belief can be traced back to ancient civilizations such as the Egyptians, Greeks, and Hindus, who all believed in the existence of an eternal soul or consciousness that could be reborn into a new body after the physical body died.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/gnosis-3/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Introduction to Kundalini Tantra</title><link>/posts/intro-kundalini/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/intro-kundalini/</guid><description>What is Kundalini?> What is Kundalini? # Kundalini is an evolutionary force of consciousness that can be awakened to explore more ways to express yourself. Some people believe it&amp;rsquo;s evil while others believe it&amp;rsquo;s divine, which is discussed in the next post of this series.
Awakening your Kundalini> Awakening your Kundalini # Kundalini awakening refers to the activation and ascent of Kundalini energy, a type of spiritual energy believed to reside within the human body.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/intro-kundalini/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Is Kundalini Evil?</title><link>/posts/is-kundalini-evil/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/is-kundalini-evil/</guid><description>We broke down the processes of Kundalini in the last post, now that we have an idea of what Kundalini is, we can now go ahead and question whether or not Kundalini is a force of positivity or negativity.
Kundalini&amp;rsquo;s Polarity> Kundalini&amp;rsquo;s Polarity # The textbook definition of Kundalini is &amp;ldquo;negatively polarized creative energy&amp;rdquo;. Let&amp;rsquo;s go over some ways this could be true:
They do teach us to use our Crown Chakra to make the energy positively polarized, but that requires an opening of the Crown Chakra; and some people don&amp;rsquo;t even have these!</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/is-kundalini-evil/cover.png"/></item><item><title>A Full Guide to Energy</title><link>/posts/energy-work/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/energy-work/</guid><description>Prerequisites> Prerequisites # Read the Grounding your energy article before starting this course. Thank you!
Developing your Toolset> Developing your Toolset # 1. Perception> 1. Perception # The first thing you should learn is how your mind signatures energy.
Do you see emotions as colors? Do you see entities in a humanoid form? Do you hear voices? Does your nose randomly get irritated by a smell seemingly from nowhere? Whichever sense has the extra sensory perception ability will tell you which clairvoyant or psychic ability you possess.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/energy-work/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Grounding your energy 🌴</title><link>/posts/grounding-your-energy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/grounding-your-energy/</guid><description>Grounding oneself energetically is a practice that can help to reduce stress and anxiety, and increase feelings of calm and clarity. It can also be helpful for connecting with the present moment and the physical world. Here are some steps you can follow to ground yourself energetically:
Find a comfortable, quiet place to sit or stand. You can do this indoors or outdoors, depending on your preference.
Take a few deep breaths and focus on the sensation of the breath moving in and out of your body.</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/posts/grounding-your-energy/cover.png"/></item></channel></rss>