<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gnosis on Heliacal Club</title>
    <link>/series/gnosis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gnosis on Heliacal Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/series/gnosis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christ Consciousness &amp; Light Bodies (Merkaba)</title>
      <link>/posts/gnosis-merkaba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gnosis-merkaba/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s Christ Consciousness?&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Christ Consciousness? # Christ Consciousness is a state of consciousness in which you have formed a union with your divine self which is also a part of your creative mind.
Your abilities from this life and maybe some from other lifetimes feel as natural as breathing air during christ consciousness.
To achieve this state, you must learn how to flow with the divinity within your mind. You must be able to recognize your conscious mind from your subconscious mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Planetary Energy Grid</title>
      <link>/posts/gnosis-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gnosis-1/</guid>
      <description>Introspections&gt;Introspections # There exists a blue etheric energy grid surrounding our planet. I theorize it&amp;rsquo;s responsible for keeping Souls trapped in the planetary matrix (system). This is also a common belief for those who have discovered the grid actually zapping our mental atom upon death resulting in what you have faith in being presented to you. TODO: This topic needs more research and a lot more discussion. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transmigration of the Human Soul</title>
      <link>/posts/gnosis-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gnosis-3/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s Soul Transmigration?&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Soul Transmigration? # The transmigration of the human soul, also known as reincarnation or rebirth, is a concept that has been embraced by spiritual traditions around the world for thousands of years. The origins of this belief can be traced back to ancient civilizations such as the Egyptians, Greeks, and Hindus, who all believed in the existence of an eternal soul or consciousness that could be reborn into a new body after the physical body died.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
